[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "You don't -- you were at the baby shower and you don't remember one was a girl and one was a boy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CD", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "CD", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "My humble apologies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "ANNON: I'm good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Did you know what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Yes, it was a few things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Was there a moment when you thought, I'm in real trouble here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I've tried to be optimistic the entire time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Are you doing that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I have to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Why have you wanted to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Oh, for so many reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "Now, more importantly, how is your lovely wife?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "JJR", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "She is amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "And she pleased or not very pleased that you are now horizontal for six hours more in the day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "She actually is more pleased because we're both horizontal next to each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mariah"]}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ":", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Elaborate on that for me and what did you mean by that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "It was quite interesting, because when we found the news out, I was in the hospital in -- we were looking at -- watching CNN in my hospital bed, and you know, Mariah took it extremely hard, and, you know, because not only was that someone who was her peer, it's also a close friend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "It's very true, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Has this whole experience for you made you reevaluate your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Absolutely, 100 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Any other compliments?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "ANNON: Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "So there you go --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "-- has managed to achieve the impossible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "What was the idea behind this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Well, as a pastor, helping people, I answer a lot of questions, we do a lot of counseling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "But only in marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Only in marriage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "So you -- you never had sex before marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "I did and I was wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "But why was -- why should it be one rule for her and one rule for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "CC", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "I think I was selfish and I think I was being a hypocrite.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Do you think -- given you're so traditional, do you think a woman's place is really at home, looking after children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "I think it depends on the woman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "What's your position on that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Yes, we do have a section in there on contraception.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "Yes, but I mean, should you be so bending with your religious positions and (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", ":", "NNP", ":", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Yes, well for me, honestly, it goes back to the Bible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "I mean you're not your average pastor, are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Is that part of the problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "I think we should take Jesus seriously.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Do you think you're a tolerant kind of guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "I love people very much and it's -- it's --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 422, "question": "But do you preach tolerance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "I've preached that we should love our neighbor, that we should accept --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "What -- what do you mean by tolerance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Tolerating people who may have a lifestyle or a belief that you don't agree with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "What did you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "To be honest with you, I haven't seen the whole thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 441, "question": "I mean do you think that homosexuality is a sin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "The Bible says, on six occasions --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "I believe that all sex outside of heterosexual marriage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "But given eighty states in America now have legalized gay marriage, that's fine, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Well, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 454, "question": "I mean, no one's taking much account of the anti- fornication laws, are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Yes, I do -- I don't want to be the one to enforce those laws or go around --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "So let's get to the point where there is one day a vote, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Would I officiate same-sex weddings and things of that nature?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "-- right?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NNS", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "RP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "How are you functioning on a daily basis now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "I'm going to tell you, in some ways, but for the grace of God, but also for the fact that I literally had decided -- I had a choice about 12 years ago, either live down to the expectations of doctors who told me I would be in a wheelchair four years; this disease is so devastating, you may as well give up; you've got to stop working.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "What have you done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "I have changed my diet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "And it can be any vegetables?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Pick any fruits you want and any vegetables.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "It's all completely healthy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "All completely healthy, all natural.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "There's spinach in that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Spinach.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "How are we going to fix America from a business point of view, in the way that you would with your diet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "You got it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "You mean the Rush Limbaugh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "What do you do with it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "We remove it from the community.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "Why did you choose this road?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "When I'm watching those supercells go right over these small communities, I want to be here to help.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["two and a half years ago"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Air America"]}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "Why do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "It's very interesting, because in the last few days, I don't know why the media decided to deflect Rush Limbaugh's comment and put something I said two and a half years ago on Air America in this context.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "If you were an economic political doctor and you could treat America right now, what are the key things that need to be done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "America has been in a national depression.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "WP", "NN", "PRP", ",", "TO", "DT", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 794, "question": "Has the aspiration of being a celebrity now taken over almost anything else in life for young people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 795, "answer": "My friend, there's nothing -- there's not one thing on television that doesn't reward you and try to make you a excellent, from being the garbage man to the rattlesnake biter to the one who bit you, to the -- everybody.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]